<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cache Valley Communities</title><link>https://www.cachevalley.co/</link><description>Recent content on Cache Valley Communities</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.cachevalley.co/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>WAB Warming Center</title><link>https://www.cachevalley.co/p/wab-warming-center/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.cachevalley.co/p/wab-warming-center/</guid><description>&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>This was taken directly from the &lt;a class="link" href="https://wabwarmingcenter.org" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>WAB Warming Center&lt;/a> website. We are in no way affiliated with the WAB Warming Center. We are simply sharing their information to help spread the word about this awesome community resource.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If you would like to learn more about the WAB Warming Center, please visit their &lt;a class="link" href="https://wabwarmingcenter.org" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>official website&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h2 id="our-mission">Our Mission
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>The &lt;strong>William A. Burnard (W.A.B.) Warming Center&lt;/strong> is dedicated to strengthening our community by offering warmth, safety, and care to unhoused individuals and families during the coldest months of the year in &lt;strong>Cache Valley, Utah&lt;/strong>. Our center is a sanctuary for those in need, providing a safe space to escape freezing temperatures and access critical resources.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="who-do-we-serve">Who Do We Serve?
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>The W.A.B. Warming Center serves &lt;strong>individuals and families&lt;/strong> experiencing homelessness. Families with children are welcome, but parents will need to sign an agreement that ensures their children will stay with them at all times during their visit. Volunteers and staff are on hand to offer friendly, active supervision while the center is in operation, ensuring the safety and well-being of all guests.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="our-vision">Our Vision
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>We believe in a community where &lt;strong>every person has inherent dignity and worth&lt;/strong>. Our vision is that &lt;strong>no one will spend a single night unsheltered and alone&lt;/strong> during the winter months in Cache Valley. We are committed to ensuring that every person in our community has access to the support and care they need to stay safe during the cold weather season.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>Learn More About the W.A.B. Warming Center:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>&lt;a class="link" href="https://wabwarmingcenter.org" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Official Website&lt;/a>&lt;/strong>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Cache Tech Community Meetup - January 2025</title><link>https://www.cachevalley.co/p/cache-tech-meetup-january-2025/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 00:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.cachevalley.co/p/cache-tech-meetup-january-2025/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://www.cachevalley.co/p/cache-tech-meetup-january-2025/image_870x_67799e80a280c.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Cache Tech Community Meetup - January 2025" />&lt;p>The &lt;strong>Cache Tech Community&lt;/strong> returns this January! We&amp;rsquo;re excited to announce our upcoming event on &lt;strong>Saturday, January 25, 2025&lt;/strong>, from &lt;strong>1:30 PM – 2:45 PM (MST)&lt;/strong> at &lt;strong>Community Room A, Logan Library&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>01/05/2025 - Edited to add time and location.&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Join our &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.cachevalley.co/why-you-should-join-our-official-discord-server-a-hub-for-updates-engagement-and-community-connection" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Discord community&lt;/a> to stay connected with fellow tech enthusiasts!&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="event-details">Event Details:
&lt;/h3>&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Date&lt;/strong>: Saturday, January 25, 2025&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Time&lt;/strong>: 1:30 PM – 2:45 PM (MST)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Location&lt;/strong>: Community Room A, Logan Library&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>We’ve got an exciting new format this month! Here&amp;rsquo;s what you can expect:&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="part-1-general-meetup-45-minutes">Part 1: General Meetup (45 minutes)
&lt;/h3>&lt;p>We&amp;rsquo;ll kick things off with an open discussion on navigating the tech world. Whether you’re pursuing formal education, self-learning, or growing through community-driven opportunities, we’d love to hear your story! This is your chance to share experiences, exchange ideas, and explore potential mentorship opportunities.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>All skill levels and ages are welcome—there&amp;rsquo;s something for everyone!&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="part-2-technical-deep-dive-45-minutes">Part 2: Technical Deep Dive (45 minutes)
&lt;/h3>&lt;p>In the second half, we’ll dive into the fascinating world of &lt;strong>mobile forensics&lt;/strong>! We’ll host a live demonstration on performing forensic analysis of an iPhone using the &lt;strong>Mobile Verification Toolkit (MVT)&lt;/strong>, a powerful tool for identifying spyware and malware.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Key highlights include:&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Creating and decrypting local backups of iOS devices.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Scanning backups for signs of spyware or malicious software.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Analyzing common attack vectors for mobile devices.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>A live demo showcasing how an iPhone can be compromised in under 30 minutes.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Discussion on mobile malware detection and mitigation strategies for iOS and Android.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Examining the security risks posed by the environment-sensing features of mobile devices.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="who-should-attend">Who Should Attend?
&lt;/h3>&lt;p>This event is open to everyone—no exceptions! Whether you’re a beginner, self-taught, or an experienced tech professional, there’s something here for you.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Bring your curiosity, questions, and enthusiasm—let’s learn, connect, and grow together!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Stay tuned for further updates&lt;/strong> on the event’s time and location. We look forward to seeing you there!&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>We’re excited for the return of the Cache Tech Community, and we can&amp;rsquo;t wait to kick off the year with all of you!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Why You Should Join Our Official Discord Server</title><link>https://www.cachevalley.co/p/why-you-should-join-our-discord/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 00:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.cachevalley.co/p/why-you-should-join-our-discord/</guid><description>&lt;p>Are you looking for a place to stay updated, get involved, and connect with others who share your passions? Our &lt;strong>official Discord server&lt;/strong> is the perfect spot for that! Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a newcomer or a long-time member, this server offers a variety of benefits that will enhance your experience and keep you engaged with the community. Here are some key reasons why you should join:&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="1-stay-updated-on-the-latest-news">1. Stay Updated on the Latest News
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>One of the biggest advantages of joining our official Discord server is the instant access to updates and announcements. From news about upcoming events, changes to policies, or new features, you&amp;rsquo;ll never miss an important update. The server serves as a centralized hub for all things related to the community, so you can always stay informed.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="2-get-involved-and-engage-with-others">2. Get Involved and Engage with Others
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>Discord is a fantastic platform for connecting with others, and our server is no exception. You’ll have the opportunity to meet like-minded individuals, share your experiences, and participate in discussions that matter to you. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re looking to network or just make new friends, the server makes it easy to get involved in meaningful ways.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="3-ask-questions-and-get-expert-advice">3. Ask Questions and Get Expert Advice
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>Have a burning question about a topic or need advice on something? Our server is the perfect place to ask. The community is full of people eager to share their knowledge, whether it’s tech-related, event planning, or something more niche. There’s always someone ready to help, so don’t hesitate to ask your questions!&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="4-showcase-your-community-or-event">4. Showcase Your Community or Event
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>Running a community or planning an event? We offer dedicated spaces to help you get noticed! By joining our Discord, you can post information about your own community, event, or project, giving you a chance to connect with others who might be interested. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s promoting a group, sharing an event, or highlighting a community resource, our server is a great platform to get the word out and build connections.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="5-promote-your-community-resource">5. Promote Your Community Resource
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>If you&amp;rsquo;ve created a resource that could benefit others—whether it’s a guide, tool, or informative article—you can share it with the server. Our community thrives on collaboration, and sharing your resources can help others while also building your reputation within the group.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="6-network-and-collaborate-with-others">6. Network and Collaborate with Others
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>Collaboration is key in any vibrant community, and our Discord server is designed to foster just that. Whether you’re looking to collaborate on a project, discuss new ideas, or brainstorm solutions to problems, the server is a great place to build relationships with others who share your goals.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="7-and-much-more">7. And Much More!
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>The benefits don’t stop there! By joining our official server, you’ll also get exclusive access to events, giveaways, and special features. As the community grows, we’re constantly adding new channels and opportunities for members to get involved and make the most of their experience.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="conclusion">Conclusion
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a space to connect, learn, and grow, our &lt;strong>official Discord server&lt;/strong> is the place to be. From staying updated with the latest news to promoting your own community, there are countless opportunities to engage and get involved.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>So don’t wait—join us today and become part of a dynamic, supportive, and active community!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="https://discord.com/invite/YNkqmVGZbSk" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Join the official Discord server now!&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see you there!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How to Spot and Avoid Scams</title><link>https://www.cachevalley.co/p/how-to-spot-and-avoid-scams/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.cachevalley.co/p/how-to-spot-and-avoid-scams/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;strong>First posted on &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.brentdalling.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>brentdalling.com&lt;/a>&lt;/strong>&lt;br>
Find articles like it on &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.brentdalling.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>www.brentdalling.com&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h3 id="tldr-how-to-spot-and-avoid-scams">TL;DR: How to Spot and Avoid Scams
&lt;/h3>&lt;p>Scams are becoming more sophisticated, using urgency, emotional manipulation, and promises of quick rewards to trick you. To avoid falling victim, be cautious of unsolicited messages, requests for personal information, and offers that seem too good to be true. Always verify the source, look for red flags like unprofessional language or suspicious payment methods, and take your time before acting. Trust your instincts, protect your personal details, and report any suspicious activity. By staying vigilant and informed, you can safeguard yourself against scammers.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h3 id="getting-started">Getting Started
&lt;/h3>&lt;p>In today’s world, scams are becoming increasingly sophisticated, preying on both our emotions and instincts. Whether it’s through a fraudulent email, an unexpected phone call, or a misleading social media ad, scams can take many forms. Recognizing how they operate and learning how to spot them is essential for protecting your personal information, finances, and peace of mind. Here’s how to spot and avoid scams effectively.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h3 id="1-understand-the-psychology-behind-scams">1. Understand the Psychology Behind Scams
&lt;/h3>&lt;p>Scammers often rely on psychology to manipulate victims. One of the most common tactics is creating a sense of urgency. Scammers make their offers seem time-sensitive, demanding immediate action. Whether it’s a limited-time sale, an urgent debt collection, or an emergency situation requiring quick financial help, the goal is to cloud your judgment by pushing you to act impulsively. Always take a moment to pause and think: &amp;ldquo;Is this really as urgent as it seems?&amp;rdquo; Scammers want you to act without thinking, so don&amp;rsquo;t fall for the rush.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h3 id="2-watch-out-for-unsolicited-messages">2. Watch Out for Unsolicited Messages
&lt;/h3>&lt;p>One of the most common ways scammers reach out is through unsolicited messages. You may receive an unexpected email, text message, or phone call, often pretending to be from someone you know or a trusted company. These messages often ask you to provide personal information, verify an account, or even click on a link. If you did not initiate the contact, it’s a red flag. Remember that legitimate organizations will never ask for sensitive information through these channels. Always verify the source before responding.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h3 id="3-verify-the-source">3. Verify the Source
&lt;/h3>&lt;p>Scammers frequently impersonate legitimate companies or institutions. A well-crafted email or website can mimic the look and feel of a trusted organization, tricking you into believing it’s authentic. If you receive a message from your bank or any service, don’t respond to the contact details provided in the message. Instead, go directly to the official website or call the known customer service number to check the validity of the message. A quick search of the company&amp;rsquo;s website or calling them directly can help you avoid falling victim to fraudulent schemes.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h3 id="like-what-youre-reading">Like what you&amp;rsquo;re reading?
&lt;/h3>&lt;p>&lt;blockqoute>Checkout this &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.cachevalley.co" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>free community event in Logan, UT on January 25th!&lt;/a> - It&amp;rsquo;s a free tech meetup and live iPhone hacking demonstration and tutorial. Find out more on &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.cachevalley.co" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>www.cachevalley.co&lt;/a>.&lt;/blockqoute>&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h3 id="4-look-for-red-flags-in-communication">4. Look for Red Flags in Communication
&lt;/h3>&lt;p>Scammers often overlook basic details when creating fraudulent communications. This includes spelling errors, unusual grammar, or odd formatting in emails or texts. While these may seem like small issues, they can be significant indicators of a scam. Another red flag is overly emotional language designed to elicit a reaction. Whether it’s fear (e.g., “Your account will be suspended if you don’t act now”) or excitement (e.g., “You’ve won a prize!”), take a step back. Genuine businesses will maintain a professional tone and won’t pressure you with these tactics.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h3 id="5-be-cautious-with-too-good-to-be-true-offers">5. Be Cautious with Too-Good-To-Be-True Offers
&lt;/h3>&lt;p>If something sounds too good to be true, it probably is. Scammers often lure victims with offers that seem too generous to resist, such as &amp;ldquo;exclusive discounts&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;prizes&amp;rdquo; that require payment upfront. The promise of large sums of money, gifts, or urgent financial opportunities is designed to make you act quickly. If you find yourself questioning the legitimacy of an offer, it’s best to research the offer or consult others before proceeding. Legitimate opportunities are transparent and will not demand urgent actions or payments.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h3 id="6-protect-your-personal-information">6. Protect Your Personal Information
&lt;/h3>&lt;p>Your personal data is a valuable target for scammers. Never give out your Social Security number, credit card details, or passwords unless you are certain of the legitimacy of the request. Scammers may ask for sensitive information under the guise of helping you with a problem or providing a service, such as &amp;ldquo;updating&amp;rdquo; your account. Always be cautious and avoid providing personal information unless you know the request is authentic and you are on a secure, trusted platform.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h3 id="7-use-secure-payment-methods">7. Use Secure Payment Methods
&lt;/h3>&lt;p>When making purchases online, always use secure payment methods such as credit cards or well-known payment systems like PayPal. These platforms offer fraud protection and the ability to dispute charges if something goes wrong. Avoid wire transfers or sending money through peer-to-peer apps when dealing with unknown sellers or offers. Scammers often ask for payments through these methods because they’re difficult to trace, leaving you without recourse if things go wrong.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h3 id="8-look-for-the-savior-complex-in-scams">8. Look for the &amp;ldquo;Savior&amp;rdquo; Complex in Scams
&lt;/h3>&lt;p>Scammers often position themselves as the &amp;ldquo;savior&amp;rdquo; of a situation. They might claim to have an urgent solution to a problem, promising to fix a financial issue, save a loved one, or offer a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity. They will create a narrative where you feel as though you must act immediately to avoid disaster or miss out on something extraordinary. This manipulation plays on your emotions and can make you act irrationally. Always take a step back and ask yourself, “Do I really need to take action right now?” Scams thrive on urgency, and calm, thoughtful reflection is your best defense.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h3 id="9-keep-software-and-security-updated">9. Keep Software and Security Updated
&lt;/h3>&lt;p>Your digital security is just as important as your financial and personal safety. Scammers often use malware, phishing sites, and malicious software to steal sensitive information. Ensure your computer, phone, and other devices have up-to-date security software, and regularly install updates to protect against new threats. Using strong, unique passwords and enabling two-factor authentication wherever possible can also help safeguard your accounts from unauthorized access.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h3 id="10-trust-your-instincts-and-report-suspicious-activity">10. Trust Your Instincts and Report Suspicious Activity
&lt;/h3>&lt;p>Sometimes, the best defense against a scam is your gut feeling. If something doesn’t feel right, take the time to investigate further. Research the company or individual, check for reviews, and ask trusted friends or family members for advice. If you suspect that you&amp;rsquo;ve encountered a scam, report it to the authorities or a consumer protection agency, such as the Federal Trade Commission (FTC). The more information that’s shared about scams, the easier it will be to protect others from falling victim to similar schemes.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h3 id="scam-likelihood-checklist">Scam Likelihood Checklist
&lt;/h3>&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Unsolicited Contact&lt;/strong>: Were you contacted unexpectedly by someone you don’t know or weren’t expecting?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Sense of Urgency&lt;/strong>: Is there pressure to act immediately (e.g., threats, limited-time offers)?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Request for Personal Information&lt;/strong>: Are they asking for sensitive details (e.g., Social Security number, bank details)?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Too-Good-To-Be-True Offers&lt;/strong>: Does the offer seem unrealistic or promise huge rewards for little effort?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Suspicious Links/Attachments&lt;/strong>: Were you asked to click a suspicious link or download an unknown attachment?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Unprofessional Language&lt;/strong>: Is there poor grammar, spelling errors, or unprofessional tone?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Unclear Contact Info&lt;/strong>: Is the contact information mismatched or difficult to verify?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Irregular Payment Methods&lt;/strong>: Are you asked to pay through unusual methods (e.g., wire transfer, gift cards)?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Vague Information&lt;/strong>: Is the source or company hard to verify, or is the offer unclear?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Emotional Manipulation&lt;/strong>: Is the communication playing on emotions (fear, excitement, urgency)?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Secrecy Requests&lt;/strong>: Are you told to keep the situation secret or not share details with others?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Lack of Transparency&lt;/strong>: Are important details vague or withheld?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Exclusive Offers&lt;/strong>: Were you told you are the “only one” or “exclusive winner” without proof?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Immediate Payment Requests&lt;/strong>: Are you pressured to pay before receiving goods or services?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Suspicious Website URL&lt;/strong>: Does the website look fake or have a strange/misspelled URL?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h3 id="scam-likelihood">Scam Likelihood:
&lt;/h3>&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>0-3 Yes Answers&lt;/strong>: Low likelihood – Stay cautious.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>4-7 Yes Answers&lt;/strong>: Moderate likelihood – Verify before proceeding.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>8+ Yes Answers&lt;/strong>: High likelihood – Avoid and report.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>Stay vigilant, and don’t let scammers trick you into making hasty decisions that could lead to significant harm.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Shortcodes</title><link>https://www.cachevalley.co/p/shortcodes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.cachevalley.co/p/shortcodes/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://www.cachevalley.co/p/shortcodes/cover.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Shortcodes" />&lt;p>For more details, check out the &lt;a class="link" href="https://stack.jimmycai.com/writing/shortcodes" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>documentation&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="bilibili-video">Bilibili video
&lt;/h2>
&lt;div class="video-wrapper">
&lt;iframe src="https://player.bilibili.com/player.html?as_wide=1&amp;amp;high_quality=1&amp;amp;page=1&amp;bvid=BV1d4411N7zD"
scrolling="no"
frameborder="no"
framespacing="0"
allowfullscreen="true"
>
&lt;/iframe>
&lt;/div>
&lt;h2 id="tencent-video">Tencent video
&lt;/h2>
&lt;div class="video-wrapper">
&lt;iframe src="https://v.qq.com/txp/iframe/player.html?vid=g0014r3khdw&amp;auto=0"
scrolling="no"
frameborder="no"
framespacing="0"
allowfullscreen="true"
>
&lt;/iframe>
&lt;/div>
&lt;h2 id="youtube-video">YouTube video
&lt;/h2>&lt;div class="video-wrapper">
&lt;iframe loading="lazy"
src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/0qwALOOvUik"
allowfullscreen
title="YouTube Video"
>
&lt;/iframe>
&lt;/div>
&lt;h2 id="generic-video-file">Generic video file
&lt;/h2>&lt;div class="video-wrapper">
&lt;video
controls
src="https://www.w3schools.com/tags/movie.mp4"
>
&lt;p>
Your browser doesn't support HTML5 video. Here is a
&lt;a href="https://www.w3schools.com/tags/movie.mp4">link to the video&lt;/a> instead.
&lt;/p>
&lt;/video>
&lt;/div>
&lt;h2 id="gist">Gist
&lt;/h2>&lt;script src="https://gist.github.com/CaiJimmy/e2751a943de10b2a5b3a8a6c2120cb86.js">&lt;/script>
&lt;h2 id="gitlab">GitLab
&lt;/h2>&lt;script
type="application/javascript"
src="https://gitlab.com/-/snippets/2589724.js"
>&lt;/script>
&lt;h2 id="quote">Quote
&lt;/h2>&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat. Duis aute irure dolor in reprehenderit in voluptate velit esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur. Excepteur sint occaecat cupidatat non proident, sunt in culpa qui officia deserunt mollit anim id est laborum.&lt;/p>&lt;span class="cite">&lt;span>― &lt;/span>&lt;span>A famous person, &lt;/span>&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Book">&lt;cite>The book they wrote&lt;/cite>&lt;/a>&lt;/span>&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;hr>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Photo by &lt;a class="link" href="https://unsplash.com/@codioful" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Codioful&lt;/a> on &lt;a class="link" href="https://unsplash.com/photos/WDSN62Qdxuk" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Unsplash&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote></description></item><item><title>Archives</title><link>https://www.cachevalley.co/archives/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.cachevalley.co/archives/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Community Resources</title><link>https://www.cachevalley.co/community-resources/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.cachevalley.co/community-resources/</guid><description>&lt;p>This page is dedicated to the community resources that we use to collaborate and build together. Below you&amp;rsquo;ll find links to helpful tools, templates, and other important resources that power our community’s operations.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="github">GitHub
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="https://github.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>GitHub&lt;/a> is where all the magic happens. This is our community GitHub server, where you can access all the resources needed for digital operations, from project repositories to documentation and templates.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In fact, this very website is hosted on GitHub. You can find the source code for this website &lt;a class="link" href="https://github.com/CacheValleyCommunities" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>here&lt;/a>. You can also help contribute to make it better!&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="osint---domain--ip-check">OSINT - Domain / IP Check
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="https:/security.cachevalley.co" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>OSINT - Domain / IP Check&lt;/a> is a tool that allows you to check the domain or IP address of a website. It provides information about the domain, such as the owner, location, and more. This tool is useful for conducting op`en-source intelligence (OSINT) investigations and gathering information about a website.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The reason this is being made available to the community is to help local businesses, students, and hobbyists secure their websites. Usage of this tool is free and open to the public. However, Individual users are liable for their own actions and should use this tool responsibly.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This tool is capable of providing the following information:&lt;/p>
&lt;table>
&lt;thead>
&lt;tr>
&lt;th>Supported Checks&lt;/th>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/thead>
&lt;tbody>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>IP Info&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>SSL Chain&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>DNS Records&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Cookies&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Crawl Rules&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Headers&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Quality Metrics&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Server Location&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Associated Hosts&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Redirect Chain&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>TXT Records&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Server Status&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Open Ports&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Traceroute&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Carbon Footprint&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Server Info&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Whois Lookup&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Domain Info&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>DNS Security Extensions&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Site Features&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>HTTP Strict Transport Security&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>DNS Server&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Tech Stack&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Listed Pages&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Security.txt&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Linked Pages&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Social Tags&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Email Configuration&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Firewall Detection&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>HTTP Security Features&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Archive History&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Global Ranking&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Block Detection&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Malware &amp;amp; Phishing Detection&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>TLS Cipher Suites&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>TLS Security Config&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>TLS Handshake Simulation&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Screenshot&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>+ more!&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/tbody>
&lt;/table>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://www.cachevalley.co/community-resources/1.png"
width="3024"
height="1730"
srcset="https://www.cachevalley.co/community-resources/1_hu3654032162916004171.png 480w, https://www.cachevalley.co/community-resources/1_hu14049866914590490797.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="OSINT - Domain / IP Check"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="174"
data-flex-basis="419px"
>
&lt;img src="https://www.cachevalley.co/community-resources/2.png"
width="3024"
height="1726"
srcset="https://www.cachevalley.co/community-resources/2_hu13090216202570316814.png 480w, https://www.cachevalley.co/community-resources/2_hu3438839198410710394.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="OSINT - Domain / IP Check"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="175"
data-flex-basis="420px"
>
&lt;img src="https://www.cachevalley.co/community-resources/3.png"
width="3024"
height="1724"
srcset="https://www.cachevalley.co/community-resources/3_hu4997453509957965285.png 480w, https://www.cachevalley.co/community-resources/3_hu14251624273129304588.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="OSINT - Domain / IP Check"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="175"
data-flex-basis="420px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="it-tools">IT Tools
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="https://tools.cachevalley.co" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>IT Tools&lt;/a> is a collection of tools that are useful for IT professionals. It includes encoding, decoding, and hashing tools, as well as a variety of other useful utilities. This collection of tools is designed to help IT professionals and developers work more efficiently and effectively.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This has been made available to the community to support small businesses, students, and hobbyists in their IT projects. The tools are free to use and open to the public. However, individual users are responsible for their own actions and should use these tools responsibly.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The following tools are available in the collection:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://www.cachevalley.co/community-resources/4.png"
width="3024"
height="1724"
srcset="https://www.cachevalley.co/community-resources/4_hu9445134286972627398.png 480w, https://www.cachevalley.co/community-resources/4_hu11242606306903470583.png 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="IT Tools"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="175"
data-flex-basis="420px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>You can always come back here to find more valuable community resources. Stay tuned for updates!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Contributors</title><link>https://www.cachevalley.co/contributors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.cachevalley.co/contributors/</guid><description>&lt;p>This page is dedicated to the talented individuals who have contributed to the development and growth of this website and its resources. Below you&amp;rsquo;ll find a list of contributors who have played a significant role in making this project a success.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="contributors">Contributors
&lt;/h2>&lt;h3 id="brent-dallinghttpsbrentdallingcom">&lt;a class="link" href="https://brentdalling.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Brent Dalling&lt;/a>
&lt;/h3>&lt;p>&lt;em>Community Member&lt;/em>&lt;br>
Brent is the primary contributor to the website, responsible for overseeing the project&amp;rsquo;s direction, design, and development. You can find more about him on his &lt;a class="link" href="https://brentdalling.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>personal website&lt;/a> and see his GitHub contributions &lt;a class="link" href="https://github.com/bvdalling" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>here&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>We also encourage everyone in the community to contribute, whether it’s with code, ideas, bug reports, or anything else! Find out more about how to get involved on our &lt;a class="link" href="https://github.com/CacheValleyCommunities" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>GitHub repository&lt;/a> and start contributing today.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>If you&amp;rsquo;d like to contribute or learn more about the individuals behind this project, feel free to reach out or explore their personal pages linked above. We’re always open to new contributions!&lt;/p>
&lt;hr></description></item><item><title>Search</title><link>https://www.cachevalley.co/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.cachevalley.co/search/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>