<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Community Event on Cache Valley Communities</title><link>https://www.cachevalley.co/tags/community-event/</link><description>Recent content in Community Event on Cache Valley Communities</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 00:16:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.cachevalley.co/tags/community-event/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cache Tech Community Meetup - January 2025</title><link>https://www.cachevalley.co/p/cache-tech-meetup-january-2025/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 00:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.cachevalley.co/p/cache-tech-meetup-january-2025/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://www.cachevalley.co/p/cache-tech-meetup-january-2025/image_870x_67799e80a280c.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Cache Tech Community Meetup - January 2025" />&lt;p>The &lt;strong>Cache Tech Community&lt;/strong> returns this January! We&amp;rsquo;re excited to announce our upcoming event on &lt;strong>Saturday, January 25, 2025&lt;/strong>, from &lt;strong>1:30 PM – 2:45 PM (MST)&lt;/strong> at &lt;strong>Community Room A, Logan Library&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>01/05/2025 - Edited to add time and location.&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Join our &lt;a class="link" href="https://discord.com/invite/YNkqmVGZbSk" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Discord community&lt;/a> to stay connected with fellow tech enthusiasts!&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="event-details">Event Details:
&lt;/h3>&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Date&lt;/strong>: Saturday, January 25, 2025&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Time&lt;/strong>: 1:30 PM – 2:45 PM (MST)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Location&lt;/strong>: Community Room A, Logan Library&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>We’ve got an exciting new format this month! Here&amp;rsquo;s what you can expect:&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="part-1-general-meetup-45-minutes">Part 1: General Meetup (45 minutes)
&lt;/h3>&lt;p>We&amp;rsquo;ll kick things off with an open discussion on navigating the tech world. Whether you’re pursuing formal education, self-learning, or growing through community-driven opportunities, we’d love to hear your story! This is your chance to share experiences, exchange ideas, and explore potential mentorship opportunities.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>All skill levels and ages are welcome—there&amp;rsquo;s something for everyone!&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="part-2-technical-deep-dive-45-minutes">Part 2: Technical Deep Dive (45 minutes)
&lt;/h3>&lt;p>In the second half, we’ll dive into the fascinating world of &lt;strong>mobile forensics&lt;/strong>! We’ll host a live demonstration on performing forensic analysis of an iPhone using the &lt;strong>Mobile Verification Toolkit (MVT)&lt;/strong>, a powerful tool for identifying spyware and malware.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Key highlights include:&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Creating and decrypting local backups of iOS devices.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Scanning backups for signs of spyware or malicious software.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Analyzing common attack vectors for mobile devices.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>A live demo showcasing how an iPhone can be compromised in under 30 minutes.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Discussion on mobile malware detection and mitigation strategies for iOS and Android.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Examining the security risks posed by the environment-sensing features of mobile devices.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="who-should-attend">Who Should Attend?
&lt;/h3>&lt;p>This event is open to everyone—no exceptions! Whether you’re a beginner, self-taught, or an experienced tech professional, there’s something here for you.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Bring your curiosity, questions, and enthusiasm—let’s learn, connect, and grow together!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Stay tuned for further updates&lt;/strong> on the event’s time and location. We look forward to seeing you there!&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>We’re excited for the return of the Cache Tech Community, and we can&amp;rsquo;t wait to kick off the year with all of you!&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>